猛男主厨 美味出炉
Hot food from a hot man.
麦克斯 我那区有个女人问
Max, a woman in my section wants to know
咱们有没有无谷蛋白的食物
if we do anything gluten-free.
怎么回答
What do I tell her?
跟她说 别假装对谷蛋白过敏
Tell her she's not allergic to gluten,
来掩饰自己的饮食失调症
she's just masking an eating disorder.
各位 打起精神
Look alive, people.
总汇三明治 汉堡配中薯
Club sandwich, burger, medium,
以及给赌鬼的鲜虾沙拉
and a shrimp salad for the gamblin' man.
我要的盐和胡椒呢
I asked for salt and pepper.
我的蛋黄酱和芥末酱呢
I wanted mayonnaise and mustard.
你忘了我的无糖汽水
You forgot my diet soda.
抱歉 马上给您拿...
I'm sorry, I'll be right back with--
瞧 这是啥
Oh, what?
姐是有两把刷子的
Never doubt me.
最后一张单了 厄尔
Here's my last check, Earl.
瞧 麦克斯
Look here, Max.
那女的刚塞了她电话号码给我
That lady just slipped me her number.
老子难道还缺另一个绝经白师奶
Like i need another menopausal white woman
像猫发情挠窗一样地对我发情吗
scratchin' at my window like a cat in heat.
天啊 我爱死钱了
God, I love money.
我懂 真遗憾钱不爱你了
I know, I'm so sorry it broke up with you.
瞧 这周Ipad2上市了
Look! This week's new Ipad just came out.
赶紧去广而搞之吧
Spread the words.
是"告"啊
Word.
"高"啊
Word!
我是从电线杆上的广告学的
I saw that on the wire.
麦克斯 都三周了
Max, three weeks in a row,
你还没接受我脸书的加好友请求
you have not yet accepted my request to be a Facebook friend.
麦克斯 我跟你说话呢
Max? I am talking to you.
戴着耳机呢 听不见
I didn't hear you, I have my earbuds in.
那这是什么
What are these?
不到黄河心不死 不见棺材不掉泪吗
Okay, you had to bust a move, and get "the truth" on my ass?
好吧 那我就送你一程
Fine, let's go there.
憨 我永远都不会加你为好友的
Han, I'm never gonna be your Facebook friend.
呜
Woo!
万箭穿心啊
Hard to hear.
没关系 我加了你 憨
Well, I accepted you, Han.
谢谢 你让我心花怒放
Yes, thank you. You make my heart sing.
呜
Woo!
血还吧嗒吧嗒流呢
Hurts me still.
刚才就像看人拿木棒打爆小海豹一样
That was like watching someone club a baby seal.
干嘛不加他好友啊
Why wouldn't you just say yes to his friend request?
因为我从来不上脸书 加了干啥
Because I never check Facebook, why would I?
上脸书好让我零五年的同事
So some girl I worked at a movie theater with in 2005
能给我留言 今天下雨 她"灰常郁闷"吗
can tell me it's raining and she's "totes bummed?"
卡洛琳 最好检查下你脸书主页哟
Caroline! Better check Facebook page.
没准刚有人在你主页上贴了点东西呢
Maybe someone just post on your wall.
"李憨在二十五张照片中圈出了你"
"Han Lee has tagged you in 25 photos?"
想借我的海豹棒一用吗
Wanna borrow my seal club yet?
太伤人了
That stings.
我爸锒铛入狱后 我的脸书好友骤减了三百人
I've lost like 300 Facebook friends since my father was arrested.
没准你爸在牢里也交了这么多新好友呢
Well, your father's probably made that many new friends in prison,
有失必有得嘛
so it all evens out.
好了 要走了吗
Okay, ready to go?
必须得走吗 外面热死了
Do we have to? It's so hot outside.
高温什么时候有这么吓人了
When did heat get so hot?
与其奋力挣扎 不如闭眼享受
Stop fighting it, just give in to it.
奇怪 我怎么用了强奸犯的台词
I don't know why I'm quoting a rapist.
我们不能再待会儿吗 家里都没有空调
Can't we just stay a little bit longer? We don't have any A.C. At home.
我有空调 你们可以过来用
I have an A.C. You girls can use.
你的空调能用啊
You have an air conditioner that works?
当然能用
Oh, it works.
你这台空调像刚吃过蒜味香肠似的
That's like an A.C. That just had salami.
这台空调还内建另一根"大香肠"呢
There's more salami where that came from.
我的脚疼死了
And my feet hurt.
别踩"高跷"上班了 买双平民休闲鞋吧
Well, you gotta stop wearing those stilts, and get a pair of skechers,
破产女招待的基本配置
like normal broke-ass waitresses.
平民休闲鞋 这话你也说得出口
Skechers? How dare you.
再说了 我没钱买新鞋
Besides, I can't afford new shoes.
这双花了我九百块呢
These cost $900.
你的脚不是疼 是遭天谴
Well, then that's not pain, that's karma.
我会帮你的 好吧
Look, I will help you out, okay?
我知道有个地方 花小钱也能买名牌
I know a place we can go that has designer things at good prices.
就像巴尼时尚卖场吗
Like a Barney's Warehouse?
差不多吧
Kind of.
善心二手店
The Goodwill?
欢迎来到我的地盘
Welcome to my place!
你居然带我来买二手货
We're shopping at the Goodwill?
我还真以为你要带我去买好货呢
You led me to believe we were real-shopping.
我猜到了
I know.
我就想看你来到这家店时的表情
I couldn't wait to see your face when you saw this place.
再做一次
Do the face again.
爽死我了
I love it!
好吧 这是什么味儿
Okay, what's that smell?
这股穷酸味以后就是你的味儿
It's gonna be your smell from now on.
听好了 我告诉你好货在哪
Now, pay attention, I know where the good stuff is.
我知道好货在哪里
I know where the good stuff is.
在麦迪逊大街和五七街那儿[高档店街]
Madison and 57th.
跟我来
Follow me.
心机女会把心头好藏起来 等回头再买
Clever bitches hide stuff they want to come back and buy,
因为有时她们连三块钱都没有
'cause sometimes they don't have $3 to buy it at the time.
谁会没有三块钱啊
Who doesn't have $3?
比如你呀
You.
上周我把一件超帅的复古外套
Last week I hid a dope vintage blazer
藏到柜子后面的抽屉里
in the back of a nightstand, and
瞧
here it is!
六块钱 心机女 手到擒来
Six bucks, clever bitch. Bang, bang!
好吧 既然都来了 我就好好淘淘吧
All right, well, we're here. I'm gonna make the best of it,
不过得先找个没有刨冰渍的篮子
but first I need a basket without a sno-cone in it.
翠丽丝[像上层社会名字]
Hey, Trish.
平时不穿 去乡村俱乐部时穿
Not for day-to-day, but at the country club.
你搞笑啊 不过还真没说错
You're kidding, but you're right.
看上某件衣服后 记得检查口袋有没有药丸
When you find something, check the pockets for pills.
我有次在市区旧衣店
At a thrift store downtown
我找到了一颗紫色药丸
I found a purple one once, and took it.
吃完我昏睡了八个小时
Fell asleep for eight hours.
就当是我那年的年假了
That was my vacation that year.
好耶 鞋子
Yay, shoes!
真不敢相信我居然在二手店里欢呼
I can't believe I just said, "yay", in Goodwill.
先别高兴太早 鞋子可能会有异味
Look, don't freak. Shoes can be funky,
但我家有一瓶特殊喷雾 一喷异味全无
but I have a special spray at home that makes them like new.
能救破店的鞋 难不成是巫师的药水吗
Did you get it from a wizard?
我的天啊
Oh, my God.
天呀 这双名牌高跟鞋是我的
Oh, my God, these Brian Atwoods were mine.
因为穿着它见过两次报
I donated these to charity,
所以我就捐给慈善机构了
'cause I was photographed wearing them twice.
我当时可是花了八百大洋买的 现在只值八块
Okay, they were $800 when I bought them, now they're $8?
就像我
Like me.
身价暴跌
I'm $8.
天啊
Oh, my god.
我只值八块
I'm $8.
我被降价了
I've been reduced.
抱歉 贫穷感突然排山倒海地袭来
I'm sorry, it just all became so real to me.
这事实好难接受
I mean, I can't believe it.
你没看见我在哭吗
Didn't you see me crying?
善心二手店每天都有大把人哭
Lots of people cry at Goodwill.
去法国就会吃蜗牛 来这里就会眼泪流
You go to France, you eat snails. You come here, you cry.
太怪了吧 你居然完全没反应
That's odd, you didn't even react.
听到别人哭 你得有点反应啊
You need to react when people cry.
我有啊 我翻了个白眼
I did, I rolled my eyes.
终有一天 你会学会泪往心里流
Look, eventually, you'll learn to do that on the inside.
好吧 我告诉你
Okay, well, just FYI,
以前我在其他闺蜜面前哭时
when i used to cry in front of my other girlfriends,
她们会说 小琳琳 你在哭什么呢
they'd be like, "what you cryin' about, C-line? "
妹子 你可是又犀利又迷人哟
Look at you, girl, you're fierce, you got your glam on.
你的闺蜜都是黑人变装癖娘炮吧
Are your girlfriends black drag queens?
哇 这件鼓击乐队的T恤好赞呀
Oh, awesome Strokes tee.
我有去那场演唱会 当时买不起这T恤
I went to this concert, but I couldn't afford the shirt.
所以我的话题到此结束了
Oh, we're done with me.
我大三那年暑假去看他们的巡演
I went to see them on this tour the summer after my junior year.
那是个燥热的夜晚 我溜出家里
It was a really warm night, and I snuck out of the house,
然后我们一起做...
and we all ma-- ahem.
没啥啦
Whatever.
做了什么呀
And what?
说呀 那晚是不是发生了什么好事
What, did something great happen the night you got the T?
瞧我这样 像是有好事光临过吗
Look at me, does it look like something great ever happens?
这T恤不错 是我先看上的
Hey, cute tee. Had my eye on it.
我过去叫朋友来帮我看看
I was just bringin' my girl back to see it.
她刚去厕所了
She was in the bathroom.
我刚在吐
I had to throw up.
-乖乖交出来 -你又不是不知道规矩
- So hand it over. - You know the rule.
出其不意 攻其不备
Turn the back on the rack, you're under attack.
别怪我 这是二手店的法则
That's not me, that's the law of the 'will.
就是 你俩快滚吧
Yeah, you better walk away.
刚真是剑拔弩张啊
That was intense.
这在二手店是老生常谈了
Just another Wednesday at the 'will.
你说好货是被人藏起来的 是吧
You said to look in things, right?
麦克斯 瞧 初战告捷
Max, look. On my first try!
干得好 藏这货的人该七窍生烟了
Ooh, slick. Whoever hid those is gonna be pissed.
检查质量
Quality check.
布料完好 胯部无不明污渍
Fabric sturdy, no mysterious crotch stains,
不错啊 少女妙探
nice work, Nancy Drew.
瞧 还是名牌呢
And look, they're designer.
零九年夏装 售价三百五十美元
Summer 2009. $350.
而今天我的到手价是
And for me today...
五块钱 我就喜欢这种降价
$5. That's a reduction I like.
你好啊 玛丽亚
Hi, Maria.
最近好吗 麦克斯
How are you, Max?
还行 你妈妈好吗
I'm good, how's your mom doin'?
挺好 她很谢谢你做的小蛋糕
Good. She really appreciated the cupcakes you made her.
你好 玛丽亚 我是麦克斯的朋友卡洛琳
Hi, Maria, I'm Caroline, Max's friend.
这双鞋能不能算便宜点
Any way we can get the price down a bit for these?
鉴於这鞋况
I think $8 is steep,
要价八美元有点太贵了
considering their condition.
我碰巧得知 这只鞋跟换过了
I happen to know the heel has been replaced.
我真不敢相信你居然开口还价
I cannot believe you're trying to shoe her down.
-六块钱卖给你吧 -成交
- I can do $6. - Deal.
高兴了吧 你跟慈善机构杀价
Oh, you happy? You haggled a charity.
把人家善心二手店弄成死心二手店
You're turning Goodwill into bad will.
我的T恤不见了
My T-shirt's gone.
不在篮子里
It's not here.
我猜肯定是那个波多黎各女
I bet it was that Puerto Rican girl,
她一直猛盯着那衣服
who was-- who was eyeing it.
玛丽亚 麻烦叫下保安
Maria, can we call security?
肯定有摄像头拍到那个贼
I'm sure one of the cameras must have captured the theft.
摄像头 你以为这是哪里 塔吉特百货吗
Cameras? What do you think this is, Target?
没了就没了 卡洛琳
It's gone, Caroline.
她肯定是趁我欣赏
She must have stolen it while I was watching you
你的五块钱傻乐舞时偷走的
do your stupid $5 dance.
不备的是你 干嘛攻击我
I didn't turn my back on the rack, why am I under attack?
这就是为什么我一个人逛街
See, this is why I shop alone,
一个人吃饭
this is why I eat alone,
一个人先走的原因
this is why I'm leaving alone.
玛丽亚 我来结账吧
Maria, I'll pay for these.
不必拿盒子装 用纸裹上就行
You don't have to box them,you can just use tissue paper.
说完就觉得自己好白痴
Even as I'm saying this, I know it's not gonna happen.
嘿 栗宝
Hey, Chestnut.
体温高得就跟孕妇一样 对吧
Hot as a mother, right?
好点了吗
Better, right?
* 这里热气腾腾 *
* It's gettin' hot in here *
* 适宜宽衣解带 *
* So hot so take off all your clothes *
* 浑身热血沸腾 *
* I am gettin' so hot *
* 我要宽衣解带 *
* I'm gonna take my clothes off *
你最好还是小声点
You might want to keep your voice down.
这座楼有三个记录在案的性侵者
This building has three registered sex offenders.
* 这里热气腾腾 *
* It's gettin' hot in here *
* 让那T恤随汗去 *
* So leave all that Strokes tee shirt drama behind *
拜托 今晚难得休息
Come on, it's our night off.
我们去有空调的地方一醉方休吧
Let's go get drunk in air conditioning.
连酒钱都不用带
We won't even have to pay for drinks.
这双白花花的大腿就能搞定
These "shotes" is gonna pay for our drinks.
你现在活脱就是个要价五块钱的妓女
You are literally a $5 whore right now.
走吧
Come on.
你好 强尼
Hi, Johnny.
不是叫你那悲剧肥臀离我店里远点吗
I thought I told you to keep your dumb, tragic ass out of here.
老娘的屁股才不悲剧
The only thing that isn't tragic about me is my ass.
这个金发干瘪丑女是谁
And who's the blonde, bony skank?
伙计 不要伤及无辜
Dude, she's not in on this.
抱歉 女士 我是麦克斯的朋友强尼
I'm so sorry, Miss. I'm Johnny, I'm Max's friend.
我是被吓死的卡洛琳
I'm Caroline. I'm freaked out.
我俩经常这么干
This is something we do.
会想起我们家庭的"温馨"
To remind us of our families.
先失陪啦
Excuse me for a second.
跟那俩家伙击掌聊妞 他们就会多给小费
These guys tip more if I high-five 'em when we talk about chicks.
-阴道 -万岁
- Vagina! - Yeah!
闺蜜 你的酒保朋友蛮可爱的嘛
Girl, your bartender friend is cute.
瞧他的双臂 猛男呀
Look at those arms. Nice guns.
他不光是个小酒保 这家伙有份正经职业
He's not just a bartender, this dude is legit.
他是街头艺术家 艺名是"电子图档"
He's a street artist, goes by "Jpeg".
现在他不照样在这儿切莱姆 洗杯子
Well, right now he's cutting up limes and cleaning glasses.
现在你这个富家女
Well, you're an heiress
不也照样跟糊掉的食物和过期的面包为伍
who's slinging burnt hash and stale toast.
-一针见血 -体无完肤
- Touche. - Douch-ay.
那位先生赠的美酒一杯 美言一句
These are from the gentleman with a sweet note,
"小俏臀 大美胸"
"nice ass, nice rack."
喝龙舌兰叫声就这样
If that's your tequila noise,
你高潮的时候还得了
God knows what your orgasm sounds like.
表情一致 默不作声
Same face, no sound.
天啊
Oh, my God.
冤家路窄啊 是二手店的那骚货
I can't believe it, it's the girl from the 'will.
我帮你讨回公道 姐妹儿
I got your back, gir-r-r.
她要干嘛
What is she doin'?
她以为去过二手店就能当悍妹子了
She thinks Goodwill has made her tough.
你好呀
How are you?
我想跟你谈谈今天在善心二手店那件T恤
I just wanted to talk to you about that shirt at the Goodwill.
我的朋友真的很喜欢它
See, my friend really wanted it,
结果却被你的朋友抢走了
and, well, your friend has it.
你说什么呢 贱货
What are you sayin', bitch?
虽然初次见面时 没留下好印象
Okay, I think we might have got off on the wrong foot.
那要老娘给你留一脚印象吗 贱货
Do you want to feel my foot, bitch?
看来大家都知道你的爱用词了
Well, I guess we know what your favorite word is.
我这秀发可是天生的 贱货
Those are not extensions, bitch!
我应该制止她们 我应该制止她们
I should break this up, I should break this up.
别别别 先让她挨个四秒揍才会学乖
No, no, no, give her like four seconds to learn her lesson.
哎呦 放手 放手
Okay, ow! All right. All right!
时间到 快去
Okay, okay, okay.
好了 别闹了 没事了
Okay, come on, come on. It's okay.
我这秀发可是天生的 贱货
Those are not extensions, bitch!
你怎么还在笑 这事一点都不好笑
Are you still laughing, 'cause it wasn't funny.
太好笑了 你比兔八哥[卡通]还逗呢
It was so funny. It was like Looney Tunes funny.
跟兔八哥被猎枪颜射了一样好笑
It was like Bugs Bunny getting shot in the face funny.
而且你这兔八哥 还企图跟猎枪讲道理
Only in your version, bugs bunny tries to have a dialogue with the shotgun.
我想帮你把T恤要回来
I was trying to get your T-shirt back.
我想你拥有那衣服
I wanted you to have it,
你在二手店看到它时两眼都放光了
because you lit up at the 'will when you saw it.
我才不会放光
I do not light up, okay?
我内心阴暗 希望之光已灭
There's no light inside me.
我发出的光 可能是某年夏天我在铁轨边
What you're seeing is probably radiation from the summer
收集铀管 身上残留的辐射光吧
I collected uranium tubes by the train tracks.
那年挣了不少呢
That was good money.
谢谢你为我出头 卡洛琳 别客气 麦克斯
Thanks for looking out for me, Caroline. You're welcome, Max.
不过是件T恤 没了就算了
It's a T-shirt, it's gone.
我从不乱放感情的
I don't get attached to things.
我的美甲都被那山寨凯特·方迪给整没了
My nail practically got torn off back there by Kat Von D-minus.
看来今晚睡觉得忍受美甲翘翘的了
I'm gonna have to sleep with it elevated.
这附近有做美甲的地方吗
Is there a nail place around here?
这里是纽约嘛 没准就在...
Well, this is new york, so there's probably gonna be one right...
前方 生活处处有惊喜呀
Here. Love when that happens.
瞧 闺蜜价买一送一 太棒了
Look, a two-for-one girlfriend special. Genius.
明天上班前一起去吧 两人同去更便宜哦
Go with me tomorrow before work, it'll be cheaper if we both go.
我不做新的不行了
I really need one.
再说了 你指甲也该修修了
Plus, you need one, too.
我去不了 我已经安排好至尊逍遥游了
Well, I can't. I have my own day of luxury already booked.
先洗衣服 然后去速食店试吃
I'm doing a laundry, and then the tasting menu at Wendy's.
来嘛 我和你 享受空调加美甲
Come on. You and me, nails, and air conditioning.
肯定不错 就这么定了 姐妹儿
It'll be fun. You're doin' it, gir-r-rl.
以前我和我的闺蜜最喜欢去做美甲了
Me and my friends used to love getting manicures.
黑人变装癖娘炮都好这一口
'Cause they are black drag queens
伙计
Hey, dude.
是不是时间到啦
It's about that time?
让我先拿上便便铲
Let me get the pooper scooper.
好咧 出征吧
All right. Let's do this.
我问你件事
Let me ask you something.
你这匹马
How is it that you, a horse,
还有卡洛琳都跟我一起住
and Caroline are both living with me,
为什么你却让我省心这么多
and you're less of a problem for me?
你来解释下吧 毕竟你俩相识已久
I mean, you tell me, you've known her longer.
她居然在布朗克斯区挑衅满身刺青的白妞
She picks a fight with a tatted-out white chick from the bronx?
她脑子有病啊
What is up with that?
我也不知道 伙计 我早就见怪不怪了
I don't know, man, I'm just used to it.
如果你会说话 大概就这声音吧
That's what you'd sound like, if you talked.
对了 我完全同意刚才你说的话
I agree with you, by the way.
你说的每一句话都是对的 麦克斯
Everything you say is right, Max.
多谢 栗宝
Thank you, Chestnut.
你真该杀了她
You should kill her.
栗宝 我不能这么做
Chestnut! I can't do that.
杀她很容易滴 我们把她宰来吃了吧
It'll be easy. We could kill her and eat her.
栗宝
Chestnut!
好了 伙计 你的拉屎宝地到了
All right, buddy, here's your spot.
快点 拉吧
Come on, do your business.
快点 小栗
Come on, ches.
快呀
Come on.
快点啦 栗宝 我今天忙得要死呢
Come on! Come on, chestnut, I got a lot of crap to do today.
看来你也要"屎"了
And so do you.
天啊 别害羞 尽量拉 伙计
Jeez, don't be shy, buddy...
这下你开心了吧
I hope you're happy.
我看起来像柬埔寨的脱衣舞娘
I look like a cambodian stripper.
她们更喜欢被人称为"乒乓射手"
They prefer to be called "ping pong ball artists."
这花了我七十块四毛三
These cost $70.43.
她逼我得做假指甲
She forced me to get tips,
再付她做假指甲的小费
and then tip her for the tips.
瞧 而且因为你没来
See, and all because you never showed up,
我拿不到买一送一的折扣
I didn't get the two-for-one discount,
还让我独自一人 苦等一个不出现的你
because I was waiting alone, for you.
麦克斯 我真的很努力想跟你成为闺蜜
Max, I have really tried to be girlfriends with you,
但显然你心里有毛病
but you obviously have some issues.
跟我进冷藏室
Follow me to the walk-in.
好 大家来摊牌
Good, let's get it out.
拿着
Here.
不是要进来谈心吗
I thought we were gonna talk.
才不是 我只是让你进来帮我拿巧克力奶油派
No, we just didn't have any chocolate cream in the case.
你为什么没来
Why didn't you show up?
你答应会来的
You told me you were gonna be there.
我有一堆屁事要忙
Well, I had a lot of crap to do.
你给我的感觉像是你会来啊
Well, you gave me the impression you were going.
有吗 我才不给人什么感觉
I gave you the impression? I don't do impressions.
等等 其实也不是 我会模仿我妈
Well, wait, that's not true, I do one, my mom.
但要模仿出她 需要一颗圣诞树
But to do that. I need a christmas tree,
一加仑伏特加 和一根点燃的香烟
a gallon of vodka, and a lit cigarette.
所以我们到底要不要做闺蜜
So are we gonna be girlfriends or not?
听着 我就直说吧
Look, I'm gonna give this to you straight up.
我真的做不了你要的那种闺蜜
I am never gonna be the type of girlfriend you're used to.
我不会当姐妹 也不是你的姐妹儿
I am not your gir-r-r, or your gir-r-rl,
我也不是会为了折扣
and I am definitely not someone's
而跟你一起做美甲的人
two-for-one girlfriend crap at a nail store.
老实说 你就当我是个爷们吧
In fact, think of me as a dude.
那 咱俩没事吧
So-o-o, are we good?
嗯 没事
Yeah. We good.
我懂 你天生不是当闺蜜的料
I get it. You're not a girl's girl.
好 很好
Okay, good.
我可是块当闺蜜的料哟
I can be a girl's girl.
卡洛琳 请你的马别再来占我便宜了
Caroline, please do not take advantage of me with your horse.
什么
What?
垃圾清理公司现在跟我多要钱
My trash pick up company charged me extra,
因为我的大垃圾桶里全是你的马粪
because my dumpster is full of all your horse droppings.
这怎么可能
How would that be possible?
我看见你的好朋友麦克斯 天天早上帮你遛马
I see your good friend, Max, walking your horse every morning
还把马粪全扔我垃圾桶里
and dropping droppings in my dumpster.
-你好吗 -好啊
- Hi. - Hello.
你今天早上帮我遛马了吗
Did you walk my horse today?
是啊 每天早上都遛
Yeah, and every other morning.
真贴心 怎么不早点告诉我
That's so sweet. I wish I had known.
是要我怎么说 去你脸书主页上留言吗
Well, what was I gonna do, post it on your facebook wall?
"唉 今儿个又遛马 恶心屎我了"
"Ha, walked a horse again today. Totes gross."
再说了 除了我还会有别人干吗
Besides, who did you think was doing it?
以前凡事都不用我动手
I've always just had things done for me,
我也从没想过事儿都是谁做的
I've never really thought about the people doing them.
可我天生穷苦命 凡事都得亲力亲为
Yeah, and I've never had things done for me, so I just do them.
比如现在 我在做咖啡
Like now, how I'm making the coffee,
你就在旁边傻站闲着
and you're just standing here watching me.
你还是应该早点说的 我好谢谢你
Still, I wish you would have told me,so I could say thank you.
这不是我的风格
Well, it's not really my style.
你还真是个难捉摸的爷们
You are one complicated dude.
上菜 罗宋汤
Pick up, borscht.
-我靠 -怎么了
- Unbelievable. - What?
两位好呀 鼓击乐队T恤真好看
How you guys doin'? Cute Strokes tee.
可能我穿会更好看
Probably look better on me,
因为这衣服本来就是我的
considering it's mine.
一不留神 人事已非 贱货[西语]
You snooze, you lose, puta.
巧舌如簧啊
Nice language!
你就用这舌头跟你基爆的小男友舌吻吗
You kiss your obviously closeted boyfriend with that mouth?
不过姐现在也不想要了
You know what? I wouldn't even want it now.
被你穿过后
Now that it's been on you,
鼓击乐队看起来跟肯尼·基一样瞎
might as well have been a Kenny G shirt.
现在姐要走人了
And now I walk.
你不能让她得逞啊
You can't just let her win.
算了 就这样吧
Forget it, it's over.
罗宋汤 上菜 快上菜
Borscht! Pick up, pick up.
我马上为您服务
I'll be right with you.
蠢货
Idiota!
这衣服花了我四块钱呢 我要杀了你[西语]
Esta camiseta me costo cuatro dolares! Te voy a cortar.
抱歉 都怪我不好[西语]
Lo siento. Todo es mi culpa.
我才来第一周 还有点笨手笨脚
I'm still a little clumsy, it's my first week.
我给您端杯苏打水来洗洗 但说真的
I'll bring you some soda water, but seriously,
污渍没洗掉 你男人就掉进别的男人怀抱了
your boyfriend will come out before that borscht stain does.
-干得漂亮 -就是
- That was awesome. - Yeah.
我向来只做事 不废话
I kinda just do stuff.
就像刚那样
Like I just did,
我下手 而你却在旁边傻站闲着
while you were standing there watching me.
谢谢你 好姐妹儿
Thank you, gir-r-rlfriend.
-糟糕 -怎么 她来报仇了吗
- Oh,no - What, is she coming for me?
快跑
Run.